{"cards":[{"mId":"c5e13fae-4e18-4e8b-857c-83ab453e3167","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Overweight","mBack":"Fat"},{"mId":"519fc97f-574b-40d1-90b0-b28051e383ed","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Obesity","mBack":"Extrememly fat or overweight."},{"mId":"023e0091-02a5-4de3-97f9-2b8539b6d19a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Eating Disorder","mBack":"A mental illness in which people eat far too little or far too much food and are unhappy with their bodies."},{"mId":"8d3e6a3b-d79a-4081-8e79-2b044c049fd0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Nutrients","mBack":"Any substance which plants or animals need in order to live and grow."},{"mId":"89a10aea-2e6e-4aa9-8a37-b26ec0cdcf5e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Diet","mBack":"When someone eats less food, or only particular types of food, because they want to become thinner or for medical reasons."},{"mId":"0d23a8a7-852c-4d27-a05c-dc51c3354dd6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Overeating","mBack":"Eating more than your body needs."},{"mId":"57752748-47c2-4344-882a-e68034ac5f62","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Ingredients","mBack":"A food that is used with other foods in the preparation of a particular dish."},{"mId":"b7244643-1946-4f9b-9112-b3a8a107a566","mCardType":"text","mFront":"","mBack":"A condition that makes a person become ill or develop skin or breathing problems because they have eaten certain foods or been near certain substances.Allergy"},{"mId":"11267da7-55f4-40e6-9dc7-edb13bb96d26","mCardType":"A substance which is added to food in order to improve its taste or appearance or to preserve it.","mFront":"11267da7-55f4-40e6-9dc7-edb13bb96d26","mBack":"Additive"},{"mId":"61d2d6b3-fa04-43e6-a950-53d31bc01f5e","mCardType":"To stop something from happening.","mFront":"61d2d6b3-fa04-43e6-a950-53d31bc01f5e","mBack":"Prevent"},{"mId":"9c967f7f-7c09-4183-a151-0f6d3e055752","mCardType":"Often changing and being different.","mFront":"9c967f7f-7c09-4183-a151-0f6d3e055752","mBack":"Variety"},{"mId":"3c5b385d-f2d6-40ff-b346-e924d1c44b26","mCardType":"When you want to eat food.","mFront":"3c5b385d-f2d6-40ff-b346-e924d1c44b26","mBack":"Appetite"},{"mId":"4f299751-ab90-46d2-958f-90cca5e1fb0e","mCardType":"A substance in foods such as fruit, vegetables and brown bread, which travels through the body as waste and helps the contents of the bowels to pass through the body easily","mFront":"4f299751-ab90-46d2-958f-90cca5e1fb0e","mBack":"Fibre"},{"mId":"7cdef754-1074-42aa-a010-b3461a16c67c","mCardType":"Happening or doing something often","mFront":"7cdef754-1074-42aa-a010-b3461a16c67c","mBack":"Regular"},{"mId":"ae41f7fa-0e76-4194-bfde-5916c482299a","mCardType":"Any of a group of natural substances which are necessary in small amounts for the growth and good health of the body","mFront":"ae41f7fa-0e76-4194-bfde-5916c482299a","mBack":"Vitamins"},{"mId":"a1836f3b-8bb5-4ef5-b446-e1c3634e8115","mCardType":"A disease in which the body cannot control the level of sugar in the blood","mFront":"a1836f3b-8bb5-4ef5-b446-e1c3634e8115","mBack":"Diabetes"}]}